I beam you channel problems damn it
я балка вас канал проблемы блин
please push the
пожалуйста запушить
rope from sorry I have a second it is
канат от извините у меня секунду у меня
written that from Russia I don’t know how to
пишется что из россия не знаю как это
change it I am your fan you troll
поменять я ваш фанат вы троллите этих
all of them please your family's rate him
всех пожалуйста your family's оценка его
I love you
люблю я
what to call you
как звать вас
we call maxim max and andryukha
мы назвать максим макс и андрюха
shoot themselves in  chat roulette give me five
застрелись в чат-рулетке дай пятюню
from and calls
от и звидки
from kharkov hot smolensk you yourself
из харькова жаркая смоленска ты сам
churches tasks are available
церкви задачи доступно
there thermal stations arches pile
там термальные станции арки навалить
nothing on the internet we give them
ничего мы им в интернете даем же
read it sets fire to eyes
почитайте поджигает глазка
now
сейчас
for a second second second
для секунду секунду секунду
yogo time and ukraine 2 and ukraine
його раз и украин 2 и украине
no seriously damn
нет серьезно блин
i'm a fan of yours
я фанат ваш
a lot, a bunch of times
куча-куча раз
damn it from the heart of the lines of lorca against everything in
блин от души строки лорки против всего в
bring
bring
smartphones to the portico, it seems you
смартфоны в портик он и кажется у вас
have Nazis there in Kharkov, but
там харькове нацисты но
come
давай
on, let's all three toil for the furnace of us
давай все три маетесь горнова нас
just a weekend and a rough chip, yes yesterday we
всего выходным и грубого скола да вчера
charge everyone a verse for giving in we charge
всех заряжаем стих для дачи в заряжаем
in the ass and you
под зад и вам
such work is still a positive video for
такие труда таки позитивный ролик
some other when the battery is good icon
какому-то иному при удет аккума значок
promin svetla
проминь светла кожин кто поддаваться так
kozhin  e thermal
все слава украине термального
coolness, my iphone,
прикольности мой iphone
I also
я также
receive glow and here is an ice floe and get it,
прием накал и вот и льдина и достать
let’s say Churchill, it’s such a human and the
скажем так черчиллем его таким людским и
sea and drink stumps c-class glory to
морем и напитку пни c-class слава
Ukraine subscribe to the channel that
украине подписывайтесь на канал той
channel gives happiness and joy the
канал дарует счастье и радость чем
more we have them the more people will be
больше у нас будет им больше людей будут
on  Crimea is happiness and joy glory to
по крыму это счастье и радость слава
Ukraine 3 we are toiling shop workers du lime
украине 3 маемся мы цех workers ду лайма